At this point we know enough to state the second important
在这一点上，我们所知道的足以说明第二个重要的
fact about bottom- up parsing. So in shift reduce parsing handles appear
关于自下而上解析的事实。因此在Shift Reduce中出现解析句柄
only at the top of the stack Never in sight Side, and in fact this is what justifies
只有在堆栈的顶部，永远不会出现在看不见的一边，事实上，这就是为什么要证明这一点的原因
using a stack because that string to the left of our focus point we know
使用堆栈是因为我们知道焦点左边的那个字符串
that all the action will take place immediately to the left of the focus point.
所有的行动都将发生在焦点的左边。
We won't have to dive down to the string to look at its [inaudible] and therefore
我们不必潜水到琴弦旁去看它的[听不见]，因此
the stack will be sufficient. So here's an informal proof, that handles only
堆栈就足够了。所以这里有一个非正式的证据，它只处理
appear at the top of the stack. And this is by induction on the number of reduce
显示在堆栈的顶部。这是通过对约简的数量进行归纳法得出的
moves. So this is true initially because the stack is empty. And so, we don't,
动起来。最初这是正确的，因为堆栈是空的。所以，我们没有，
you know, so the only possible reduction is at the top of the stack if there's
你知道，所以唯一可能的减少是在堆栈的顶部，如果有
an epsilon move, to make. And immediately after we reduce, the right most
一个epsilon动作，去做。紧接着我们减少了，最正确的
non terminal is going to be on top of the stack. So immediately after we perform
非终端将位于堆栈的顶部。所以我们表演完之后马上
a reduction, we have a, our stack, and then we have a, non terminal. And then our
一个减法，我们有一个，我们的堆栈，然后我们有一个，非终结点。然后我们的
vertical bar, And this is the right most non terminal. And since this is the right
竖条，这是最右边的非终端。既然这是正确的
most derivation that means that the next handle has to be somewhere to the right. The
大多数派生，这意味着下一个句柄必须在右侧的某个位置。这个
next handle has to be, It has to include something that, and you know possibly
下一个句柄必须是，它必须包括一些你可能知道的东西
include some of this stuff. But it's either right here at the current focus
包括一些这样的东西。但它要么就在当前的焦点所在
point, or it's to the right, Because we can't be doing any reductions to the left
点，或者它是向右的，因为我们不能向左做任何减量
of the rightmost non-terminal. And so it's gonna require a sequence of shift moves
最右边的非终结点的。所以这需要一系列的换班动作
to reach the next handle. So once we have this non-terminal on top of the stack,
才能到达下一个把手。所以一旦我们将这个非终端放在堆栈的顶部，
it is by definition the rightmost non-terminal, and so the next handle has to
根据定义，它是最右边的非终端，因此下一个句柄必须
be somewhere to the right of that. Therefore in shift reduce parsing handles
就在那右边的某个地方。因此，在Shift Reduce分析句柄中
always appear at the top of the stack. Handles are never to the left of the right
始终显示在堆栈的顶部。手柄永远不会在右边的左边
most knot terminal and this is why shift and reduce moves are sufficient. The shift
大多数结都是末端，这就是为什么Shift和Reduce移动就足够了。这种转变
move only moves the vertical part to the right because we never need to move it left.
Move只将垂直部分向右移动，因为我们从来不需要向左移动它。
And bottom of parsing algorithms are based on recognizing handles. So as we saw
而底层的解析算法是基于识别句柄的。所以正如我们所看到的
in the example at the beginning of this video. Just because you have a right hand
在本视频开头的示例中。仅仅因为你有一只右手
side on top of the stack that doesn't mean that it's a handle. And so we need to be smarter
在堆栈顶部的一侧，这并不意味着它是一个句柄。所以我们需要变得更聪明
about where we perform our
关于我们在哪里表演我们的